[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2003, Dax Shepard was nominated for which of these awards?", "correct_answer": "Teen Choice Award", "incorrect_answers": ["American Comedy Award", "Emmy", "Oscar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the USA, obesity is the second leading cause of preventable death after this one.", "correct_answer": "Smoking", "incorrect_answers": ["Stress", "Drugs", "Pollution"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress voiced Judge Bumbleton in the 2007 animated movie Bee Movie?", "correct_answer": "Oprah Winfrey", "incorrect_answers": ["Ellen DeGeneres", "Renee Zellweger", "Vanessa Williams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What film company produced the 2007 film Zodiac?", "correct_answer": "Warner Brothers", "incorrect_answers": ["Touchstone", "Universal", "New Line"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why do cats seem to be attracted to the one person who doesnt like cats?", "correct_answer": "Kitty sees that person as unintimidating", "incorrect_answers": ["Kitty wants to annoy them", "Kitty thinks that person has food", "Kitty wants to win them over"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is believed to be an ancestor of the trilobites?", "correct_answer": "Spriggina", "incorrect_answers": ["Onega", "None of these", "Trichophycus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the basic chemical compound that table salt is composed of?", "correct_answer": "Sodium chloride", "incorrect_answers": ["Sodium bicarbonate", "Calcium carbonate", "Potassium iodide"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why did Cher and Christian not get together in Clueless, even though Cher had a big crush on him?", "correct_answer": "He was gay.", "incorrect_answers": ["He had another girlfriend.", "He told Cher he thought she was shallow.", "Chers dad did not want them to date."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the occupation of Jennifer Aniston\u2019s character, Grace, in the 2003 movie \u2018Bruce Almighty\u2019?", "correct_answer": "Kindergarten teacher", "incorrect_answers": ["Florist", "Waitress", "Seamstress"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country gained independence from the British Mandate for Palestine in 1948?", "correct_answer": "Israel", "incorrect_answers": ["Syria", "Sierra Leone", "Jordan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This author penned a novel centered around the mysterious Jay Gatsby who acquired an immense wealth in the hope of winning back his beloved, who married an old money millionaire, named Tom Buchanan.", "correct_answer": "Scott Fitzgerald", "incorrect_answers": ["Ernest Hemingway", "Don DeLillo", "William Faulkner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fungi are crucial for the production of which of these foods?", "correct_answer": "Bread", "incorrect_answers": ["Ketchup", "Cheese", "Creme"]}]